

Cian Ronayne

- London, UK
- (+353) 86 247 1058
- cianronaynel@gmail.com
- cian-ronayne.com

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

SEO copywriting

Google Analytics

Html & CSS

Data Analysis

CERTIFICATIONS



Fundamentals of Digital Marketing



Inbound Certified



What is Data Science?

INTERESTS











HELLO,

I have 2 years of experience working in digital marketing. Most recently, I worked as a digital marketing executive at Club Travel, updating the various travel agencies's websites, analyzing customer data to produce insights for the team, carrying competitor analysis reports, and writing content for both website content and social media activity.

Previously, I studied marketing practice at National College of Ireland, where I received a second class honours, Grade 1. There I studied a range of modules such as, digital marketing, integrated marketing communications, project management and marketing strategy.



EDUCATION

National College of Ireland

BA (Honours) in Marketing Practice, 2nd class honours grade 1.

Dublin City University

BA in International Relations, withdrew after completing 2 out of 4 years of study.

- Killester College of Further Education
 QQI level 5 ertificate in Information Technology.
- Skerries Comunity College
 Achieved 390 points in the leaving Certificate.



WORK EXPERIENCE

DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Club Travel - HRG Ireland, Dublin (Oct 2018 - Jul 2020)

DATA ENTRY CLERK

Tickets.ie, Dublin (Sep 2018 - Sep 2018)

MOVER

Two Men And A Truck, Chicago (May 2018 - Aug 2018)

FOOD & BEVERAGE ASSOCIATE

HMSHost International, Dublin Airport (Jul 2015 - Jan 2016)